[{"answer": "We want peace more than any other people.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "What does this mean for the peace process, for the Israelis, and the Palestinians?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "First I think it's a -- it's a terrible tragedy because everybody -- I look at the pictures in Japan and I think what every Israeli thinks and I think what every person in the world thinks, this could be us.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "We didn't have any civilian nuclear energy.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Are you saying that you might actually stop any kind of nuclear energy program in Israel?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "First, it didn't begin in Tunisia.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "And did you ever imagine that it would create the kind of domino effect we've been seeing?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "That you get another Iran.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "What is -- what is the nightmare scenario for you?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Egypt under Sadat and then under Mubarak kept the peace and I think that's something extraordinarily valuable.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "I mean to other people he may be a dictator, to Israel, he's been a pretty good friend, isn't he?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Well, I was -- I was concerned that we might have the opposite of what people want, and what we all want.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Were you sad to see him go?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, Gadhafi is no friend of Israel, no friend of the Jewish people.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "What do you make of what's happening there?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "ETANYAHU: I think -- I think the case of Libya is an interesting place where values and interests cohere.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "What if he doesn't go?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "I think it's one of those cases where the moral compunction as you said and the -- and the interests cohere.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Is there not a moral compunction for America, for the West generally, to get in there and sort this out?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Certainly wouldn't be against it.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "If America decided to take military action, would you support that?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "I don't think it's surprising at all.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing I've been trying to do for a long time, for -- you know, for about 15 years, I think, I was elected first time 15 years ago, and I went to speak at the -- before the joint session of the U.S. Congress.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "I mean rather than wait for other countries to intervene on your behalf, what is Israel actually doing right now to combat this incredibly serious threat?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "It's working to get them.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Do they have nuclear weapons, do you think?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "I think they're getting a lot closer.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "How close do you think they are?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Even to the extent that they are transparent, it's very clear what they're doing.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Should they be transparent about their nuclear program?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well, one of the things that we're telling people is that sanctions by themselves are not going to be enough.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What are you doing about it?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I'm talking about a credible military action that the --", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Are you talking United Nations?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Led preferably by the United States.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Led by who?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "It means action that will knock out their nuclear facilities and -- (CROSSTALK)", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "What does that constitute?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, I think the United States has proven great effectiveness and I'm going to divulge a secret to you about their capabilities.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Or could you contemplate some kind of land invasion?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "No, we always reserve the right to defend ourselves.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "And you're still the number-one target, would you act unilaterally militarily?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, we have a longstanding policy that we won't be the first to introduce nuclear weapons into the Middle East, and that hasn't changed.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Do you have nuclear weapons?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "That's our policy.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "So you don't have any?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, Iran is a signatory to the NPT.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "ORGAN: Is it right to expect countries like Iran to be transparent about their own nuclear programs if you're not transparent yourself?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "I think it's ridiculous.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "The nonproliferation treaty?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "This was horrific.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "And where are you with the investigation into the perpetrators?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Seven prime ministers have tried to get peace with the Palestinians since the peace process began in Oslo in 1993.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Doesn't part of you, Benjamin Netanyahu, look at yourself and think, I want to be the guy that makes this happen, not the guy that didn't make it happen?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Honestly, what do I think?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I'm pretty big.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "And that could be you, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, it does.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Doesn't history need people to be courageous?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Because I think that Palestinian society is split into two; those who are openly calling for Israel's destruction, like Hamas, and those who not calling openly for Israel's destruction but refuse to confront those who do.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Why isn't it happening?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I was shot rescuing --", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "You were shot yourself?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "The legacy that I want is that I helped secure the life of the Jewish state and its future.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Why would you want that legacy?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "The point I was making, though, is that it's no longer the only story in town, is it?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "If you can be sure of who your partner will be tomorrow.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Isn't that the perfect time to make this happen?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Gaza's growing now at 17 percent because we lifted all the restrictions.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "There can't be, come on?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "No, of course not.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "You wouldn't want your family living there, would you?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "First of all, there's a difference in the way that the Europeans view Israel and Americans view Israel.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "And if so, why?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "In fact, that's what they're doing.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Where does that leave you?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "You can't bypass -- you can't bypass the parties to peace.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Doesn't it?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I speak to him regularly.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "When is the last time you spoke to President Obama about this?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I think there's no question he's expressed his support for Israel, especially for Israel's security.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Is he as supportive now as he's always been?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "He's said that quite a few times.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What can I do, President Obama, to help you, Prime Minister Netanyahu, make this deal happen?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I will do that with great pleasure.", "docId": "110317pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Well, if I end up meeting your expectations, you'll have to invite me back to another interview, won't you?", "qSentId": 540}]